it. Um those are the gimmicks.
But for me, the most powerful tool for
staying alert is really remembering the
core principle of active listening.
Yes.
So, in my job, I'm an attorney. I have
to I'm not the expert on what's going on
unless it's like a pure legal question,
and it never is, right? Um,
and I just go in there and pretend I'm
an idiot and I ask all the questions.
Obsessive curiosity.
Yes. In a way.
That's right.
Okay.
In In that way, do you also present sort
of a you you show your your trust as
being like I am open to learning in this
moment as well as not being forced to
wedge in what I think I know, but you're
trying to create a open space for
communication.
You're putting some words in my mouth
here, but they're absolutely correct.